Okay, that was pretty awesome!
不错，这确实很酷炫啊
And look what you managed to accomplish!
看看你们的成果！
Please, please, please
拜托，拜托，拜托
can we do a run-through for the fashion show on it right this minute?
我们能现在就在这里做一次时装秀彩排吗？
Thought you weren't finished with the stitching on your poncho
可是你的披风都还没缝好
I am now
现在缝好了
Get started without me
你们先开始吧
I've gotta go find Twilight
我得去找下暮光
Seeing what we've been able to do here might make her embrace the new magic, too!
说不定她在看到我们的成果后也能坦然面对这新的魔法了！
Uh, not that she has any
呃，不过她也没有
I just wish you didn't tell them that ridiculous story!
我真希望你没给他们讲过那个蠢故事！
Ah, this is all too much for you!
这对你来说压力太大了！
You have to let it go!
你得学会放手！
I knew it!
我就知道！
He wants her to get rid of the camp!
他想让她卖掉营地！
Ugh!
啊！
Sunset Shimmer?
余晖烁烁？
What were you doing behind that door?
你在门后面干什么呢？
What?
啥？
Um, nothing.
啊，没什么！
I, um, lost an earring. Uh, there it is!
我-那个-耳环掉了，哈，找到了！
Hey, listen
嘿，那个
I'm glad I ran into you
很高兴正好碰到你
I really wanted to thank you
我很想谢谢你
For what?
谢什么？
For the tough love
谢你对我在感情上的开导
Telling me I should get over Twilight
告诉我我应该放下对暮光的感情
I needed to hear that
这对我帮助很大
Sure, no problem
啊，不客气
Is something wrong?
有什么不对的吗？
What?
啥？
No. Why?
没事啊
Come on, Sunset
别装了，余晖
We used to date
我们在一起过
I know when something's bothering you
我能看出来你在烦恼些什么
Okay, here's the deal
好吧，是这样的
My friend really likes someone
我的一个朋友喜欢上了一个人
but I don't think that someone is who she thinks they are
但是我觉得那个人的本性和我朋友心里的形象完全不同
I don't wanna upset my friend by telling her what I think
我怕告诉了她我的想法会让她心烦
because I also want to protect her
但因为我又想保护她
because if what I think is happening is really happening
因为如果事情真如我所想的话
then she deserves to know
她还是应该知道
You know?
懂了么？
Nnnno
完全不懂
But what I do know is that your friend is lucky
但是我知道能有你这样替人分忧的朋友
to have someone like you to look out for her
她是相当的幸运
Really?
真的？
Yeah
是啊
You know, you've changed a lot since we went out
当初我们一起的时候你还不是这样呢
You're so much... nicer
现在的你…更好了
Thanks. I'm glad you noticed
谢了，真高兴你能看出来
Uh, look, maybe you and me
那个，也许我们能…
we could start over as... friends
重新开始…从朋友做起？
Uh, uh, sounds great
嗯嗯，听起来不错
I gotta go!
我先走了
Cool, yeah!
酷，耶！
I want to start over later, too!
我也觉得现在重新开始太早了
Ah, shoot!
哦，该死！
He's definitely up to something!
他绝对在密谋着什么！
It's Sunset
是余晖
She says to meet her by the rock quarry
她说去采石场见她
I thought we weren't supposed to hike out that far
我们不是不能进入那地方吗？
She says it's important!
她说有很重要的事
What is that?
那是什么？
Shhh!
嘘！
What's going on down there?
出什么事了？
I think it's Gaia Everfree
我觉得是森灵盖亚
Or rather someone who wants us to think she's back
或者说是某个希望我们认为她回归了的人
C'mon!
走！
Whoa...
哇...
This place is beautiful
这里真漂亮
There's Equestrian magic here
这里有小马国的魔力
I can... I can feel it
我能...我能感觉得到
Wait
等等
I thought Timber was just faking there was a magical nature creature
我还以为魔法生物什么的都是云杉捏造出来的
Are you saying it's real?
现在你的意思是真的有？
Timber?
云杉？
What does he have to do with any of this?
他又是怎么和这事扯上关系的？
Nothing
没关系
It's all me
都是我干的
Gloriosa?
嘉兰？
But... Timber
可是……云杉
I was sure he was the one
我还以为是他
trying to make it seem like Gaia Everfree was back
想让大家觉得森灵盖亚回来了
It was you who was trying to scare everyone away?
原来是你想吓跑大家？
I would never try to scare anyone away from Camp Everfree
我可不想吓跑森灵营地的任何一个人
My, oh my
哎呀呀
You fell behind on your payments, Gloriosa
看来你贷款还慢了啊，嘉兰金菊
I own the land now
现在这块地是我的了
Please, my great grandparents founded this place
求你了，这里是我曾祖父母创建
It's been in our family for generations!
并一代一代传下来的
You have to let the camp stay!
你不能把营地拆了！
Instead of turning it into a spa resort
也不能把这里变成一个水疗度假村
that will line my pockets with more money than this camp ever could?
然后赚到像这种小营地永远都赚不到的大把钞票？
I don't think so
我可不这么想
Please!
求您了！
I-I-I-I just need a little more time!
我－我－我－我只是需要一点时间！
Fine. I'll give you 'til the end of the month
也行，这个月底就是最后的期限
Hmph
哼
What'll I do?
我该怎么办？
Huh?
哈？
Oof
噢
Wow!
啊！
You don't know what those things are!
你不了解这些东西！
But I know what they can do!
但是我知道它们能做些什么！
I've been practicing!
我一直都在练习！
I can control their power now!
现在我已经能控制它们的力量了！
You don't know that for sure!
你又没有把握！
This is our camp, and it's being taken away!
我们的营地都要没了！
If this has to be our last week here
如果这是我们在这里度过的最后一周
I'm going to use whatever it takes to make it count!
那我就要不惜一切代价办好这最后一次！
You were using magic all over the place!
你到处使用魔法！
I had to tell them something to cover for you!
我总得跟他们说点什么幌子吧？
What did you want me to do?!
你还希望我怎么办？
I just wish you didn't tell them that ridiculous story!
我真希望你没给他们讲过这个蠢故事！
Ah, this is all too much for you!
这对你来说压力太大了！
You have to let it go!
你得学会放手！
Timber wasn't talking about letting go of the camp
云杉说的放手不是放弃营地
He was talking about you letting go of the magical geodes!
是说要你放弃这些魔法晶簇
All those things you were doing to make this week the best week ever
你一直试着让这周变成最棒露营周
Every time you used magic to do them
但你一使用魔法
you caused another problem somewhere else!
就又会出现新的问题
Timber was... covering for you!
云杉是在……为你打掩护！
How do you know what I was doing with the geodes?
你怎么知道我在用这些晶簇？
How do you know about the magic?
你怎么知道魔法的事情的？
I can see things
我能看到
Feel things
我能感觉到
Because I have magic, too
因为我也有魔法
And so does she
而且她也有
And so do our friends
我们的朋友们都有
Gloriosa, Timber wasn't wrong
嘉兰，云杉说的没错
Maybe you should stop using magic?
也许你不应该再使用魔法了
Too much of it can be dangerous if you can't control it!
强大的魔法若是控制不当是会很危险的！
Oh, I got this!
我会搞定的！
And I'm going to use it to save my camp
我要用魔法拯救我的营地
I just need more power!
我只是需要更多力量！
No!
不要！
Sorry, girls
抱歉了，两位
I know what I need to do
我很清楚自己要做什么
But I feel like we're not on the same page
不过看起来你们两个并不理解我
So...
所以……
Gloriosa!
嘉兰！
No!
不！
Where are Twilight and Sunset?
暮光和余晖呢？
They're missing our dress rehearsal
她们要错过我们的彩排了
Uh-uh
嗯哼
I suppose we can get started without them
还是不等她们了
Whenever you're ready!
准备好就开始吧！
Hmm, Told you you'd like it
都说过你会喜欢的
It's alright... I guess
我看…还行吧
I do get to keep it after camp though, right?
露营完了我就可以拿走了，对吗？
She looks... different
她看起来…变了
Yeah. She looks... taller
是啊，她看起来…变高了
This is only a preview
这只是预展而已
I've got another entire line I'll debut at the real thing
正式出演的时候我还有另外整整一系列要上呢
Why did you stop the–
你把音乐停了干－
Oh my goodness!
我的天啊！
Attention, campers!
营员们，注意！
It's Gaia Everfree!
是森灵盖亚！
She's real!
她是真的！
Aah! We're doomed!
我们完蛋啦！
Gloriosa?!
嘉兰？！
What are you doing?!
你在干什么？！
That's Gloriosa?
那是嘉兰？
Am I going crazy or are her feet not touching the ground?
是我疯了还是她真的飘起来了？
Freaky-deaky!
我怕怕！
I have an announcement to make!
我要宣布一件事！
Filthy Rich wants this to be the last session of Camp Everfree
臭钱想要让这次露营变成森灵营地所举办的最后一次露营
But don't worry
但是不要担心
I got this!
我会搞定的！
Oh, come on!
有没有搞错！
We literally just finished building that!
我们才又修好的！